iprice.my 2016-01-13

# Privacy Policy | iprice Malaysia

The website [www.iprice.my](http://www.iprice.my/) and any other related microsites and / or applications (“ **Website** ”) is operated by IPRICE GROUP SDN BHD (Company No: 1113954-D) (" **IPRICE** ", " **we** ," " **us** ," " **our** "), a company incorporated under Malaysian law. IPRICE is committed to protect your (“ **user** ”, “ **you** ”) privacy and will only use information that has been collected from you in a lawful manner.

Data protection is a matter of trust and your privacy is important to us. We shall therefore only process any Personal Data which you have provided to us in connection with your use of our Website, in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.  Defined terms used here shall bear the same meaning as defined in our Terms and Conditions, unless otherwise stated.

We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect information if it is relevant to our dealings with you. We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected. We are committed to complying with the Malaysian Personal Data Protection Act 2010 at all times.

## **Collection and  Use of Personal Information**

You can generally use and browse the Website without providing any Personal Data. However, to gain the full benefit and optimum experience of our Website and the Facility we offer, you may elect and decide  to create an to register your details with us, in which case you will be required to provide personal information such as (but not limited to) your e-mail address and gender (“ **Personal Data** ”). When doing so, we add you to our mailing list. We may use your email address to send you marketing and promotional materials which we think you may be interested in from time to time. You can at any time decide to unsubscribe from our mailing list and to stop receiving marketing and promotional materials.

## **Collection of Computer Data**

When you visit our Website, our servers will automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This data does not identify you as an individual and may include, among others:

  * Your computer's IP address
  * Browser type
  * Webpage you were visiting before you came to our site
  * The pages on our website you visit
  * The time spent on those pages, items and information searched for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics

This information is collected for analysis and evaluation in order to help us improve our website and the services provide. This data is collected anoymously and will not be used in association with any Personal Data. As part of the above, we may use various Google Analytics features. We may also uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on websites across the Internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on visitors’ past visits to our website, as well as report how ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website.

## **Links to Other Websites**

We may provide links to other websites that we do not control, these include those of our Merchants. We do not assume responsibility for the privacy practices, products, services or any other content of any websites or pages that is not under our control. We do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third-party websites. Moreover, we disclaim all responsibility for the subsequent use of an email address or any other personally identifiable information you have provided to an affiliate store or any other website we might link to that is not under our control.

## **Contact  Information for Access, Correction, Enquiries and Complaints**

Should you wish to:

  * access; or
  * make any corrections to,

the Personal Data which IPRICE has collected from you, or otherwise contact us with any enquiries or complaints in respect of your Personal Data, please feel free to contact us via e-mail at [info@ipricegroup.com](mailto:info@ipricegroup.com).

## **Security of Your  Personal Information**

We ensure that all Personal Data collected will be safely and securely stored. We protect your personal information by:

  * Restricting access to personal information;
  * Maintaining technology products to prevent unauthorized computer access; and
  * Securely destroying your personal information when it's no longer needed.

## **Disclosure of Personal  Information**

We will not share or disclose your Personal Data other than with our related companies, sister companies and Merchants who are engaged by us for processing data or which are directly related to the Website, Facility or services we are providing.

In exceptional circumstances we may be required to disclose Personal Data when required by law or when we believe in good faith that such action is necessary in order to conform with the law or comply with a court order or legal process served upon us or any of our officers or principals.

## **Changes to the  Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify and change the privacy policy at any time. Any changes to this policy will be published on our website.
